{
  "category": "funny",
  "questions":[
    {
      "question": "What state is round in one side , high in the middle and round on the other side?",
      "answer":   "A: Ohio",
      "optionA":  "A: Ohio",
      "optionB":  "B: Nigeria",
      "optionC":  "C: Ondo",
      "optionD":  "D: California"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am found at the beginning of time. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: T",
      "optionA":  "A: Nothing",
      "optionB":  "B: T",
      "optionC":  "C: 0",
      "optionD":  "D: 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is found at the center of the earth?",
      "answer":   "B: r",
      "optionA":  "A: Gravity",
      "optionB":  "B: r",
      "optionC":  "C: Alphabet",
      "optionD":  "D: e"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has ring but no finger?",
      "answer":   "B: telephone",
      "optionA":  "A: Ring",
      "optionB":  "B: telephone",
      "optionC":  "C: clock",
      "optionD":  "D: Nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is as big as the elephant but weighs 0 kg? It is the elephant's....",
      "answer":   "C: Shadow",
      "optionA":  "A: Tail",
      "optionB":  "B: Bone",
      "optionC":  "C: Shadow",
      "optionD":  "D: Eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "I see what to do but won't do it, I know where to go but won't go. What am I?",
      "answer":   "A: Lazy",
      "optionA":  "A: Lazy",
      "optionB":  "B: Brave",
      "optionC":  "C: wise",
      "optionD":  "D: Silly"
    },
    {
      "question": "Am a room, you can't enter when someone else is in. What am I ? ...... Room",
      "answer":   "A: Rest",
      "optionA":  "A: Rest",
      "optionB":  "B: Best",
      "optionC":  "C: Sitting",
      "optionD":  "D: Bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "I could speak but can't hear , I don't have eyes nor nose. What am I?",
      "answer":   "A: Loud speakers",
      "optionA":  "A: Loud speakers",
      "optionB":  "B: human",
      "optionC":  "C: Deaf",
      "optionD":  "D: Dumb"
    },
    {
      "question": "I could make the happy sad and the sad happy. I make children grow too. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Time",
      "optionA":  "A: Choice?",
      "optionB":  "B: Time",
      "optionC":  "C: Believe",
      "optionD":  "D: Opportunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is two plus two?",
      "answer":   "B: Mathematics",
      "optionA":  "A: Question",
      "optionB":  "B: Mathematics",
      "optionC":  "C: Theory",
      "optionD":  "D: Chance"
    },

    {
      "question": "I could make you laugh or cry, I can make you free or in boundage. I can actually do opposing things to people using me though everyone has me. What an I?",
      "answer":   "A: Choice",
      "optionA":  "A: Choice",
      "optionB":  "B: Tears",
      "optionC":  "C: brain",
      "optionD":  "D: Onions"
    },
    {
      "question": "I see you but you can't see me without my kind. I am big or small but size doesn't matter. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Eyes",
      "optionA":  "A: Mirror",
      "optionB":  "B: Eyes",
      "optionC":  "C: Ears",
      "optionD":  "D: Water"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am dependent on you and time and no matter what I will always be black and white. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Shadow",
      "optionA":  "A: Colour",
      "optionB":  "B: Shadow",
      "optionC":  "C: Time",
      "optionD":  "D: Choice"
    },
    {
      "question": "A child could hold ten oranges in one hand. What does he have?",
      "answer":   "B: Big hands",
      "optionA":  "A: An orange",
      "optionB":  "B: Big hands",
      "optionC":  "C: Small head",
      "optionD":  "D: Hungry stomach"
    },
    {
      "question": "A room could have everything in it green except for what?",
      "answer":   "A: Air",
      "optionA":  "A: Air",
      "optionB":  "B: Clothes",
      "optionC":  "C: Hair",
      "optionD":  "D: Door"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have eyes but can't see with it. What am I?",
      "answer":   "C: Blind",
      "optionA":  "A: Fruit",
      "optionB":  "B: Bannna",
      "optionC":  "C: Blind",
      "optionD":  "D: Unconscious"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which single letter comes before 'a' in the alphabets?",
      "answer":   "A: H",
      "optionA":  "A: H",
      "optionB":  "B: Z",
      "optionC":  "C: A",
      "optionD":  "D: Q"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am human but am sick. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Sick",
      "optionA":  "A: Unhappy",
      "optionB":  "B: Sick",
      "optionC":  "C: Human",
      "optionD":  "D: Bare handed"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am a pet I have four legs but I am not a chair. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Pet",
      "optionA":  "A: Chair",
      "optionB":  "B: Pet",
      "optionC":  "C: Table",
      "optionD":  "D: Hat"
    },
    {
      "question": "When is a torch without light? When it is...",
      "answer":   "B: Switched off",
      "optionA":  "A: Blind",
      "optionB":  "B: Switched off",
      "optionC":  "C: Soft",
      "optionD":  "D: Black"
    },

    {
      "question": "I am one but binds two together. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Wedding ring",
      "optionA":  "A: Rubber band",
      "optionB":  "B: Wedding ring",
      "optionC":  "C: Wrist watch",
      "optionD":  "D: Coat"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do some cricket players never sweat? Because they ______",
      "answer":   "C: have huge fans!",
      "optionA":  "A: eat well",
      "optionB":  "B: drink water",
      "optionC":  "C: have huge fans!",
      "optionD":  "D: never run"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is always coming, but never arrives?",
      "answer":   "D: Tomorrow",
      "optionA":  "A: Rain",
      "optionB":  "B: Luggage",
      "optionC":  "C: Visitors",
      "optionD":  "D: Tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can be broken, but is never held?",
      "answer":   "D: A promise",
      "optionA":  "A: Mirror",
      "optionB":  "B: Verse",
      "optionC":  "C: Cup",
      "optionD":  "D: A promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of pool contains no water?",
      "answer":   "A: Snooker",
      "optionA":  "A: Snooker",
      "optionB":  "B: Swimming",
      "optionC":  "C: Baby",
      "optionD":  "D: Plates"
    },
    {
      "question": "When does Friday come before Wednesday? In a/an",
      "answer":   "C: Dictionary",
      "optionA":  "A: Impossible place",
      "optionB":  "B: Word of mouth",
      "optionC":  "C: Dictionary",
      "optionD":  "D: Puzzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "What moves when you don't know though you stay in it?",
      "answer":   "B: Earth",
      "optionA":  "A: Wheel",
      "optionB":  "B: Earth",
      "optionC":  "C: Motor",
      "optionD":  "D: Tyre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is it that lives if it is fed, and dies if you give it a drink?",
      "answer":   "C: Fire",
      "optionA":  "A: Sound",
      "optionB":  "B: Air",
      "optionC":  "C: Fire",
      "optionD":  "D: Land"
    },
    {
      "question": "When is zero bigger than ninety-nine? When ninety-nine  is ____",
      "answer":   "B: Negative",
      "optionA":  "A: In a dictionary",
      "optionB":  "B: Negative",
      "optionC":  "C: Positive",
      "optionD":  "D: Neutral"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do you go to the dentist by two-thirty? Because_____",
      "answer":   "A: Sounds like tooth-Hurty",
      "optionA":  "A: Sounds like tooth-Hurty",
      "optionB":  "B: You have the chance",
      "optionC":  "C: Its near",
      "optionD":  "D: He knows his work"
    },

    {
      "question": "What do you do when you're tired ?",
      "answer":   "A: Rest",
      "optionA":  "A: Rest",
      "optionB":  "B: Bathe",
      "optionC":  "C: Watch",
      "optionD":  "D: Move"
    },
    {
      "question": "A child of my parents that is not my sister or my brother is my?",
      "answer":   "C: Self",
      "optionA":  "A: Uncle",
      "optionB":  "B: Sibling",
      "optionC":  "C: Self",
      "optionD":  "D: Shelve"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the soft do when the going is tough? Become",
      "answer":   "A: Tough",
      "optionA":  "A: Tough",
      "optionB":  "B: Shiverry",
      "optionC":  "C: Fast",
      "optionD":  "D: Hidden"
    },
    {
      "question": "What letter found after 'y' and before 'm' would spell a food?",
      "answer":   "A: A",
      "optionA":  "A: A",
      "optionB":  "B: B",
      "optionC":  "C: C",
      "optionD":  "D: D"
    },
    {
      "question": "When does the police sleep? When he's",
      "answer":   "A: Sleepy",
      "optionA":  "A: Sleepy",
      "optionB":  "B: Comes home",
      "optionC":  "C: Active",
      "optionD":  "D: Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What disappears the moment it is talked about?",
      "answer":   "A: Silence",
      "optionA":  "A: Silence",
      "optionB":  "B: Rain",
      "optionC":  "C: Wind",
      "optionD":  "D: Thought"
    },
    {
      "question": "What goes round and comes around?",
      "answer":   "C: Choice",
      "optionA":  "A: The planet",
      "optionB":  "B: The moment",
      "optionC":  "C: Choice",
      "optionD":  "D: Time"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has a blade but doesn't rotate?",
      "answer":   "B: Razor",
      "optionA":  "A: Fan",
      "optionB":  "B: Razor",
      "optionC":  "C: Engine",
      "optionD":  "D: Disk drive"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has keys but no lock, space but no room?",
      "answer":   "B: Keyboard",
      "optionA":  "A: Door",
      "optionB":  "B: Keyboard",
      "optionC":  "C: Keyholes",
      "optionD":  "D: Key holder"
    },
    {
      "question": "The word has in it and it could feed in ears?",
      "answer":   "D: Bear",
      "optionA":  "A: Hear",
      "optionB":  "B: Monster",
      "optionC":  "C: Lion",
      "optionD":  "D: Bear"
    },

    {
      "question": "Anybody wants me and anybody could have me but some become greedy on having me and even though I am not living, I am important and give authority. What am I?",
      "answer":   "C: Money",
      "optionA":  "A: Power",
      "optionB":  "B: Knowledge",
      "optionC":  "C: Money",
      "optionD":  "D: Opportunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "What body part can you never see even with a mirror?",
      "answer":   "B: The roof of the mouth",
      "optionA":  "A: The hairs",
      "optionB":  "B: The roof of the mouth",
      "optionC":  "C: The tongue",
      "optionD":  "D: The eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where does students know what time is ?",
      "answer":   "D: In the examination hall",
      "optionA":  "A: In the class",
      "optionB":  "B: In the lab",
      "optionC":  "C: At the assembly",
      "optionD":  "D: In the examination hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "When will the eagle know its worth? When ___",
      "answer":   "B: He becomes a chicken",
      "optionA":  "A: He falls",
      "optionB":  "B: He becomes a chicken",
      "optionC":  "C: He loses a feather",
      "optionD":  "D: He misses a meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which question can you never answer yes to?",
      "answer":   "C: Are you asleep",
      "optionA":  "A: Are you here?",
      "optionB":  "B: Are you going",
      "optionC":  "C: Are you asleep",
      "optionD":  "D: Do you dance?"
    },
    {
      "question": "I see an ocean but no water. Where am I?",
      "answer":   "B: In front of a world map",
      "optionA":  "A: In a dream",
      "optionB":  "B: In front of a world map",
      "optionC":  "C: In the lab",
      "optionD":  "D: In front of a TV"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is dirty after washing?",
      "answer":   "B: Clothes",
      "optionA":  "A: Nothing",
      "optionB":  "B: Clothes",
      "optionC":  "C: Bath water",
      "optionD":  "D: Hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can you hold without ever touching?",
      "answer":   "C: Conversation",
      "optionA":  "A: Air",
      "optionB":  "B: Water",
      "optionC":  "C: Conversation",
      "optionD":  "D: Prey"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is yours but most often used by others?",
      "answer":   "D: Your name",
      "optionA":  "A: A borrowed item",
      "optionB":  "B: Your clothes",
      "optionC":  "C: Your bag",
      "optionD":  "D: Your name"
    },
    {
      "question": "What falls down but is never injured?",
      "answer":   "B: Rain",
      "optionA":  "A: Shadow",
      "optionB":  "B: Rain",
      "optionC":  "C: Air",
      "optionD":  "D: Human"
    },

    {
      "question": "What gets quickly wet while drying?",
      "answer":   "B: Towel",
      "optionA":  "A: Clothes",
      "optionB":  "B: Towel",
      "optionC":  "C: Socks",
      "optionD":  "D: Singlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a Carmel with four humps?",
      "answer":   "D: Pregnant",
      "optionA":  "A: Mad",
      "optionB":  "B: Abnormal",
      "optionC":  "C: Sick",
      "optionD":  "D: Pregnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "What word in the dictionary is wrong?",
      "answer":   "B: Wrong",
      "optionA":  "A: Bad",
      "optionB":  "B: Wrong",
      "optionC":  "C: If",
      "optionD":  "D: Answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has three ways out but one way in?",
      "answer":   "C: T-shirt",
      "optionA":  "A: Y-junction",
      "optionB":  "B: School block",
      "optionC":  "C: T-shirt",
      "optionD":  "D: socks"
    },
    {
      "question": "What goes up when the water comes down?",
      "answer":   "D: Umbrella",
      "optionA":  "A: Condensation",
      "optionB":  "B: Rain",
      "optionC":  "C: Air",
      "optionD":  "D: Umbrella"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can you serve but you seldom see eaten?",
      "answer":   "C: Volleyball",
      "optionA":  "A: Rice",
      "optionB":  "B: Empty plate",
      "optionC":  "C: Volleyball",
      "optionD":  "D: Golf ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "Maybe I can hear everything but you'll never hear me say a word. Who am I?",
      "answer":   "D: Ear",
      "optionA":  "A: Deaf",
      "optionB":  "B: Dumb",
      "optionC":  "C: Jury",
      "optionD":  "D: Ear"
    },
    {
      "question": "What table can you eat?",
      "answer":   "D: Vegetable",
      "optionA":  "A: Spoilt ones",
      "optionB":  "B: Prefect-table",
      "optionC":  "C: Corn table",
      "optionD":  "D: Vegetable"
    },
    {
      "question": "What only runs and never walks, has mouth and never eats and has a bed but never sleeps?",
      "answer":   "C: River",
      "optionA":  "A: A beggar",
      "optionB":  "B: Mad man",
      "optionC":  "C: River",
      "optionD":  "D: Nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "On which side do chicken have the most feathers?",
      "answer":   "D: Outside",
      "optionA":  "A: Left side",
      "optionB":  "B: Right side",
      "optionC":  "C: Inside",
      "optionD":  "D: Outside"
    },

    {
      "question": "What's got feathers but no wings?",
      "answer":   "C: Pillow",
      "optionA":  "A: Chicken",
      "optionB":  "B: Ostrich",
      "optionC":  "C: Pillow",
      "optionD":  "D: Feather"
    },
    {
      "question": "What spends all time on the floor but never gets dirty?",
      "answer":   "C: Shadow",
      "optionA":  "A: Air",
      "optionB":  "B: Rain",
      "optionC":  "C: Shadow",
      "optionD":  "D: Wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "You can sleep on it, brush your teeth with it and sit on it. What is it?",
      "answer":   "C: Sophisticated machine( AI)",
      "optionA":  "A: Bed, chair and brush",
      "optionB":  "B: Brush, chair and bed",
      "optionC":  "C: Sophisticated machine( AI)",
      "optionD":  "D: Bed, brush and chair"
    },
    {
      "question": "What glasses shouldn't you pour apple juice?",
      "answer":   "D: Full glass",
      "optionA":  "A: Empty glass",
      "optionB":  "B: Test glass",
      "optionC":  "C: Black glass",
      "optionD":  "D: Full glass"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why can't the t-Rex clap? Because",
      "answer":   "D: He is extinct",
      "optionA":  "A: His hand are short",
      "optionB":  "B: His hands are far apart",
      "optionC":  "C: He has no hands",
      "optionD":  "D: He is extinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who earns money without working a single day ?",
      "answer":   "D: Night watchman",
      "optionA":  "A: Bill gate",
      "optionB":  "B: Dangote",
      "optionC":  "C: Thief",
      "optionD":  "D: Night watchman"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do people build new houses? Because",
      "answer":   "D: They cannot build old houses",
      "optionA":  "A: They have money",
      "optionB":  "B: They have lands",
      "optionC":  "C: It is hard to build it",
      "optionD":  "D: They cannot build old houses"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who lives an exhausting life?",
      "answer":   "C: Exhaust",
      "optionA":  "A: Night watch man",
      "optionB":  "B: Car engine",
      "optionC":  "C: Exhaust",
      "optionD":  "D: Inhaler"
    },
    {
      "question": "What goes swimming with you but never gets wet?",
      "answer":   "C: Shadow",
      "optionA":  "A: Swimming cap",
      "optionB":  "B: Rags",
      "optionC":  "C: Shadow",
      "optionD":  "D: Pool"
    },
    {
      "question": "What nails are a pain to hammer into wood?.... Nails",
      "answer":   "C: Finger",
      "optionA":  "A: Rusted",
      "optionB":  "B: New",
      "optionC":  "C: Finger",
      "optionD":  "D: Old"
    },

    {
      "question": "The more he has the less he weighs",
      "answer":   "C: Holed cheese",
      "optionA":  "A: Holes",
      "optionB":  "B: Frozen water",
      "optionC":  "C: Holed cheese",
      "optionD":  "D: Spoilt food"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who eats a lot of iron without getting sick?",
      "answer":   "B: Rust",
      "optionA":  "A: Super hero",
      "optionB":  "B: Rust",
      "optionC":  "C: Car engine",
      "optionD":  "D: Racers bike"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do Mars, Venus, Earth till Neptune make up the solar system?",
      "answer":   "C: Planet",
      "optionA":  "A: Milky way galaxy",
      "optionB":  "B: Gravitational pull",
      "optionC":  "C: Planet",
      "optionD":  "D: Sun's inner core"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did addition say to subtraction when they saw each other in Facebook?",
      "answer":   "D: Add me",
      "optionA":  "A: I hate you",
      "optionB":  "B: How are you?",
      "optionC":  "C: You are here too!",
      "optionD":  "D: Add me"
    },
    {
      "question": "What gifts should you give blind people, drunks, short sighted and nerds for Christmas?",
      "answer":   "B: Glasses",
      "optionA":  "A: Eyes",
      "optionB":  "B: Glasses",
      "optionC":  "C: Present",
      "optionD":  "D: Staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "What book do teenagers love and voluntary spend hours looking through?.",
      "answer":   "D: Facebook",
      "optionA":  "A: Novel",
      "optionB":  "B: Schools assignment",
      "optionC":  "C: Dictionary",
      "optionD":  "D: Facebook"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ended in the year 1919?",
      "answer":   "C: 1918",
      "optionA":  "A: Stone age",
      "optionB":  "B: Slavery",
      "optionC":  "C: 1918",
      "optionD":  "D: War"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the depressed math book say to the calculator, notebook and dictionary?",
      "answer":   "C: I have too many problems",
      "optionA":  "A: I am tired",
      "optionB":  "B: Get away",
      "optionC":  "C: I have too many problems",
      "optionD":  "D: Leave me alone"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many seconds are in January?",
      "answer":   "A: One",
      "optionA":  "A: One",
      "optionB":  "B: Twelve",
      "optionC":  "C: 1800",
      "optionD":  "D: None"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the right eye brow say to the left eye brow?",
      "answer":   "B: You seem surprised to see me",
      "optionA":  "A: You are far away",
      "optionB":  "B: You seem surprised to see me",
      "optionC":  "C: When I see you again?",
      "optionD":  "D: Can I come over?"
    },

    {
      "question": "What did 'A' say to 'D' when he was looking for 'E'?",
      "answer":   "C: He's BC",
      "optionA":  "A: He's not around",
      "optionB":  "B: What are you doing?",
      "optionC":  "C: He's BC",
      "optionD":  "D: Where did he go to?"
    },
    {
      "question": "People come to see me everyday despite being dirty. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Toilet",
      "optionA":  "A: Clothes",
      "optionB":  "B: Toilet",
      "optionC":  "C: River",
      "optionD":  "D: mosquito"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can be hot,  cold. I can rush, I can be still, I cold rise to the sky and I can slip through almost anything. What am I?",
      "answer":   "C: Water",
      "optionA":  "A: Air",
      "optionB":  "B: Cloud",
      "optionC":  "C: Water",
      "optionD":  "D: Ice"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have branches yet no trunk, fruit or leaves. What am I?",
      "answer":   "D: Bank",
      "optionA":  "A: Pruned tree",
      "optionB":  "B: Young shoot",
      "optionC":  "C: Seed",
      "optionD":  "D: Bank"
    },
    {
      "question": " I can fly, I can  crawl. My interpreter have hands but no wings or legs. What am I?",
      "answer":   "C: Time",
      "optionA":  "A: Bird",
      "optionB":  "B: Spider monkey",
      "optionC":  "C: Time",
      "optionD":  "D: Car"
    },
    {
      "question": "People make me, keep me, change me. I can be very dirty but it is unheard of to wash me. What am I?",
      "answer":   "A: Money",
      "optionA":  "A: Money",
      "optionB":  "B: Bag",
      "optionC":  "C: Clothes",
      "optionD":  "D: Washing machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "If a yellow race road is yellow, blue from crayon is blue and the white house is white then what colour is a green house?",
      "answer":   "D: Transparent",
      "optionA":  "A: Green",
      "optionB":  "B: White",
      "optionC":  "C: Golden",
      "optionD":  "D: Transparent"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has hands but cannot wear  gloves, a face but cannot look though it could move its hands?",
      "answer":   "D: Clock",
      "optionA":  "A: Picture",
      "optionB":  "B: Snowman",
      "optionC":  "C: Movie",
      "optionD":  "D: Clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is correct? : 1. Ostrich can fly. 2. Ostriches can fly",
      "answer":   "C: None",
      "optionA":  "A: 1",
      "optionB":  "B: 2",
      "optionC":  "C: None",
      "optionD":  "D: All"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ate nine?",
      "answer":   "C: Seven",
      "optionA":  "A: Hungry lion",
      "optionB":  "B: Deadly vultures",
      "optionC":  "C: Seven",
      "optionD":  "D: Nine wolves"
    },

    {
      "question": "I am a ball that can be rolled but never bounced or thrown. What am I?",
      "answer":   "D: Eyeball",
      "optionA":  "A: Volley bal ",
      "optionB":  "B: Tennis ball",
      "optionC":  "C: Basket ball",
      "optionD":  "D: Eyeball"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill me up with hot or cold, put anything in me I will make sure to hold it. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: Cup",
      "optionA":  "A: Table",
      "optionB":  "B: Cup",
      "optionC":  "C: River",
      "optionD":  "D: Rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "I get dirty, I get clean, I can be delicate, I can be rough. People often shake me or smack me with my own kind. What am I?",
      "answer":   "D: Hand",
      "optionA":  "A: Clothes",
      "optionB":  "B: Pillow",
      "optionC":  "C: Tie",
      "optionD":  "D: Hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am a fruit product that can talk, calculate, tweet and it is well known that I don't come cheap. What am I?... Product",
      "answer":   "A: Apple",
      "optionA":  "A: Apple",
      "optionB":  "B: Banana",
      "optionC":  "C: Mango",
      "optionD":  "D: Beans"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am a stick combined with a sweetness ball. What am I?",
      "answer":   "C: Lollipop",
      "optionA":  "A: Stick",
      "optionB":  "B: Matches",
      "optionC":  "C: Lollipop",
      "optionD":  "D: Fruit drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you give me a letter, I will not keep it for long. Boxes help pay my salary and I travel so much but never very far. What am I?",
      "answer":   "A: Postman",
      "optionA":  "A: Postman",
      "optionB":  "B: Sailor",
      "optionC":  "C: Pilot",
      "optionD":  "D: Engineer"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am a  bird, a fruit but also a person",
      "answer":   "D: Kiwi",
      "optionA":  "A: Eagle",
      "optionB":  "B: Kelvin",
      "optionC":  "C: Pineapple",
      "optionD":  "D: Kiwi"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am used in most sport, have for holes and come in different colours. There is a state that shares my name",
      "answer":   "C: Jersey",
      "optionA":  "A: Ball",
      "optionB":  "B: Helmet",
      "optionC":  "C: Jersey",
      "optionD":  "D: Boots"
    },
    {
      "question": "You can't see me nor can I be touched. You can't feel me but I can cook your lunch. What am I?",
      "answer":   "D: Microwave particle",
      "optionA":  "A: Pot",
      "optionB":  "B: Fire particle",
      "optionC":  "C: Kerosene",
      "optionD":  "D: Microwave particle"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is always late and never present now?",
      "answer":   "C: Later",
      "optionA":  "A: Late",
      "optionB":  "B: Future",
      "optionC":  "C: Later",
      "optionD":  "D: Tomorrow"
    }

  ]
}